womensarticle.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy – WomensArticle.com

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.womensarticle.com and Womens Article and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Womens Article include www.womensarticle.com. The Womens Article website is a Content Website. By using the Womens Article website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Womens Article may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Womens Article. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Womens Article website. 

Womens Article encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Womens Article so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Womens Article is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Womens Article website. 

**Use of your Personal Information**

Womens Article only attains your email address through feedburner.  All information is kept confidential and never shared.

**Use of Cookies**

The Womens Article website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Womens Article pages, or register with Womens Article site or services, a cookie helps Womens Article to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Womens Article website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Womens Article features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Womens Article services or websites you visit. 

**Children Under Thirteen**

Womens Article does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications via their feedburner account

–

**Changes to this Statement**

Womens Article will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Womens Article encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Womens Article is protecting your information. 

Effective as of January 01, 2016
